<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Integrated Chip (IC) on SPEECHCHIPS.COM</title>
    <link>https://speechchips.github.io/ics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Integrated Chip (IC) on SPEECHCHIPS.COM</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://speechchips.github.io/ics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>SC-01A</title>
      <link>https://speechchips.github.io/ics/SC-01A/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 16:22:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://speechchips.github.io/ics/SC-01A/</guid>
      <description>SC-01A #   Manufacturer: Votrax Pin Count: 22 Method: Analog Formant Inventor: Richard T. Gagnon   Datasheet    Features #   Single CMOS chip 70 bits per second 22 pin package 9 ma. current drain Wide voltage supply range Latched 5V. compatible inputs    Digital pitch level inputs Automatic inflection On-chip master clock circuit Optional external master clock Variety of voice effects Sound effects    Manufacturer Description #  The SC-01 Speech Synthesizer is a completely self-contained solid state device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SP0256-AL2</title>
      <link>https://speechchips.github.io/ics/SP0256-AL2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 16:29:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://speechchips.github.io/ics/SP0256-AL2/</guid>
      <description>SP0256-AL2 #   Manufacturer: General Instruments Pin Count: 28 Method: LPC12 Inventor: William A. Barton, John E. Stark  DATASHEET       The SP0256-AL2, also known as the &amp;ldquo;SPO256 Narrator Speech Processor&amp;rdquo;, produces all 59 phonemes of the English language plus 5 pauses of different durations. It&amp;rsquo;s part of the general &amp;ldquo;SP0&amp;rdquo; family and has many variants. Each of the phoneme&amp;rsquo;s speech patterns are individually addressable, making the SP0256-AL2 capable of saying anything that can be said in the English language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SpeakJet</title>
      <link>https://speechchips.github.io/ics/SpeakJet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 14:18:32 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://speechchips.github.io/ics/SpeakJet/</guid>
      <description>SpeakJet #   Manufacturer: Magnevation Pin Count: 18 Method: MSA Inventor: Jeff Richeson  Features #   Programmable, 5 channel synthesizer. Natural phonetic speech synthesis. DTMF and other sound effects. Programmable control of pitch, rate, bend and volume. Programmable power – up or reset announcements. Multiple modes of operation. Simple interface to microcontrollers.    Simple “Stand Alone” operation. Three programmable digital outputs. Internal 64 Byte input buffer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>